<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Saat &#8211; Osmanlı Yaldız Sanat Galerisi</title>
	<atom:link href="/product-category/clock/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Varak &#38; Restorasyon</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:24:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>tr</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Saat &#8211; Osmanlı Yaldız Sanat Galerisi</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>plaque depicting the virgin mary</title>
		<link>/product/painted-porcelain-antique-plaque-depicting-the-virgin-mary/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=87</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The delicate naturalism of this fine antique porcelain plaque is evident in the gentle expression on the Virgin's face, which calmly gazes upwards.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After the painting by Bartolomé Esteban Murillo (Spanish, 1618-1682) &#8216;The Immaculate Conception of the Venerable Ones&#8217;, 1678; housed in the Museo del Prado, Madrid, Spain.</p>
<p>Depicting the Virgin Mary in blue and white; surrounded by winged cherubs.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pair of allegorical oil paintings</title>
		<link>/product/pair-of-allegorical-oil-paintings-by-g-cornicelius/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=86</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[These fine oil paintings are a brilliant example of Cornicelius' figurative work, portraying Classically inspired personifications of the senses.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Depicting two of the five senses: Sound and Taste- Sound as a female figure draped in robes holding a tambourine in her raised left hand with a cherub by her side seated on a garland of flowers and playing the bagpipes decorated with a further garland of flowers to the upper left corner and flowers below; Taste as a male figure draped in robes holding a glass of wine in his right hand and a sceptre in his left hand with a cherub in front of him holding a garland of flowers in his raised left hand and a jug in his lowered right hand decorated with a further garland of flowers to the upper right corner, a vine with grapes through the centre and flowers below.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The succsessfull suitor</title>
		<link>/product/the-successful-suitor-19th-century-oil-painting-by-ricci/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=78</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This exceptional antique oil painting, portraying the romantic scene in breathtaking detail and stunning naturalism, is one of Ricci's finest works.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Depicting a lavish interior scene with the chosen suitor being introduced to his future wife; oil on canvas in a carved giltwood frame, signed lower right &#8216;Arturo Ricci&#8217;.</p>
<p>Canvas height 63.5cm, width 88cm</p>
<p>Frame height 84cm, width 108cm, depth 7cm</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Matched pairn</title>
		<link>/product/matched-pair-of-antique-minton-majolica-protat-ewers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=71</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[These charming antique ewers are an excellent example of fine Victorian majolica ware, which the British ceramic manufacturer Minton was famous for.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After a design by Hughes Protat, the circular bodies modelled as a barrel with entwined grapevine handles, the shoulders each applied with four Bacchic putti.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cabinet plate</title>
		<link>/product/dresden-porcelain-antique-cabinet-plate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=69</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This elegant antique porcelain plate depicts a touching image of the Madonna holding the Christ Child, both of whom gaze out into the distance.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The raised gilt leaf scrollwork border on an ivory and green background, surrounding a painting of the Madonna &amp; Child after Raphael</p>
<p>With underglazed blue crown mark to the reverse and gilded inscription &#8216;Madonna von Raphael Santio, Original in der Dresdener Jemaldegalleri&#8217;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Collectable parcel gilt porcelain</title>
		<link>/product/antique-collectable-parcel-gilt-porcelain-plate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=68</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The narrative scene on this fine antique plate encapsulates the preoccupation with the labouring man, prevalent in 19th century Russian artwork.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Circular porcelain plate, blue ground with articulated gilded rim, the centre painted with two peasants in a landscape</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>sixteen piece dessert service</title>
		<link>/product/antique-crown-derby-porcelain-sixteen-piece-dessert-service/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=67</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Crafted by prestigious English maker Royal Crown Derby, this exquisite antique dessert service would make an elegant addition to any fine dining room.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Comprising one tazze, four comports and eleven plates, each depicting birds among floral branches on ivory ground within stylised borders.</p>
<p>Diameter of all pieces 24cm; height of tazze 12cm; height of comports 6cm; height of plates 3cm</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pair of ormolu mounted sevres</title>
		<link>/product/pair-of-ormolu-mounted-sevres-style-porcelain-antique-vases/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=60</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An elegant duo, the opulence of these fine antique French vases will enhance the décor of any setting, be it a public or a private space]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On blue ground, the front with scenes depicting putti in clouds within gilt borders</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>porcelain vases</title>
		<link>/product/pair-of-ormolu-mounted-chinese-famille-verte-porcelain-vases/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 08:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=57</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The porcelain of these fine antique vases dates to the Chinese Kangxi period, and is notable for the high quality detailing of its narrative scenes.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The ormolu French, late 19th Century by Henri Vian (French, 1860-1905); the porcelain Chinese, early 18th Century, Kangxi period.</p>
<p>Each of baluster form decorated with a procession of a figure on horseback with attendants in gardens and an immortal hovering on a cloud with a baby above a bridge, the ormolu signed &#8216;h. Vian&#8217;.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sèvres clock set</title>
		<link>/product/sevres-style-antique-porcelain-and-ormolu-mounted-clock-set/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 08:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=41</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This clock set combines the beauty of Classical style with the grandeur of 19th century design, and would make a charming addition to any mantelpiece]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Comprising a central clock and pair of flanking lidded vases, the clock with central circular dial within a parcel gilt white ground porcelain vase form case painted with flying putti, and signed &#8216;E.PERNODET&#8217;, with ormolu putto cover surmount and twin satyr busts either side, supported below on an ormolu base extensively detailed with two large winged putti holding flames and floral wreath, the flanking pair of lided vases similarly decorated and painted with amorous scenes on the front and landscape scenes to the reverse, the lids topped with ormolu putti playing the lyre</p>
<p>Clock height 82cm, vases height 76cm</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
