<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>vazo &#8211; Osmanlı Yaldız Sanat Galerisi</title>
	<atom:link href="/product-tag/vase/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Varak &#38; Restorasyon</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:24:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>tr</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/favicon.png</url>
	<title>vazo &#8211; Osmanlı Yaldız Sanat Galerisi</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>plaque depicting the virgin mary</title>
		<link>/product/painted-porcelain-antique-plaque-depicting-the-virgin-mary/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=87</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The delicate naturalism of this fine antique porcelain plaque is evident in the gentle expression on the Virgin's face, which calmly gazes upwards.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After the painting by Bartolomé Esteban Murillo (Spanish, 1618-1682) &#8216;The Immaculate Conception of the Venerable Ones&#8217;, 1678; housed in the Museo del Prado, Madrid, Spain.</p>
<p>Depicting the Virgin Mary in blue and white; surrounded by winged cherubs.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pair of allegorical oil paintings</title>
		<link>/product/pair-of-allegorical-oil-paintings-by-g-cornicelius/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=86</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[These fine oil paintings are a brilliant example of Cornicelius' figurative work, portraying Classically inspired personifications of the senses.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Depicting two of the five senses: Sound and Taste- Sound as a female figure draped in robes holding a tambourine in her raised left hand with a cherub by her side seated on a garland of flowers and playing the bagpipes decorated with a further garland of flowers to the upper left corner and flowers below; Taste as a male figure draped in robes holding a glass of wine in his right hand and a sceptre in his left hand with a cherub in front of him holding a garland of flowers in his raised left hand and a jug in his lowered right hand decorated with a further garland of flowers to the upper right corner, a vine with grapes through the centre and flowers below.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The succsessfull suitor</title>
		<link>/product/the-successful-suitor-19th-century-oil-painting-by-ricci/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=78</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This exceptional antique oil painting, portraying the romantic scene in breathtaking detail and stunning naturalism, is one of Ricci's finest works.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Depicting a lavish interior scene with the chosen suitor being introduced to his future wife; oil on canvas in a carved giltwood frame, signed lower right &#8216;Arturo Ricci&#8217;.</p>
<p>Canvas height 63.5cm, width 88cm</p>
<p>Frame height 84cm, width 108cm, depth 7cm</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Collectable parcel gilt porcelain</title>
		<link>/product/antique-collectable-parcel-gilt-porcelain-plate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=68</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The narrative scene on this fine antique plate encapsulates the preoccupation with the labouring man, prevalent in 19th century Russian artwork.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Circular porcelain plate, blue ground with articulated gilded rim, the centre painted with two peasants in a landscape</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>sixteen piece dessert service</title>
		<link>/product/antique-crown-derby-porcelain-sixteen-piece-dessert-service/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=67</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Crafted by prestigious English maker Royal Crown Derby, this exquisite antique dessert service would make an elegant addition to any fine dining room.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Comprising one tazze, four comports and eleven plates, each depicting birds among floral branches on ivory ground within stylised borders.</p>
<p>Diameter of all pieces 24cm; height of tazze 12cm; height of comports 6cm; height of plates 3cm</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>krated shaped vase</title>
		<link>/product/antique-gilded-kpm-porcelain-krater-shaped-vase/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=59</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This impressive vase pays homage to the Medici family, rulers of Renaissance Florence, who highly prized vases inspired by the ancient krater form]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Medici shaped vase on a square gilt base, the upper part curved outwards with twin gilt handles, the front painted with an outdoor scene of men hunting on their horses accompanied by their hunting dogs, additionally decorated with raised gilt detailing of wreaths of foliage and pattern-work on a green ground</p>
<p>The underside with blue KPM sceptre mark</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>japanese amari porcelain vases</title>
		<link>/product/pair-of-large-ormolu-mounted-japanese-imari-porcelain-vases/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 08:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=58</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[These stunning antique Japanese vases are examples of exceptionally high quality Imari porcelain ware, which is renowned for its beauty and craftsmanship]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decorated throughout with floral patterns; the porcelain Japanese, c.1700, the ormolu French, 19th Century.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ormolu mounted sevres</title>
		<link>/product/ormolu-mounted-sevres-style-porcelain-vase-and-cover/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 08:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=55</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This exquisite Sèvres style French porcelain vase is decorated with scenes of pastoral idyll, examples of both beauty and serenity.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The dark blue ground body painted to the front with playful and amorous pastoral scenes, decorated throughout with gilt rocaille motif, mounted with twin ormolu handles shaped as winged classical female busts, surmounted by a shaped bulbous cover topped with an ormolu presentoir filled with fruit, raised on three hoof feet standing on a shaped triform base with toupie feet.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>representing water</title>
		<link>/product/large-meissen-porcelain-elements-ewer-representing-water/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 08:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=54</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This exquisite Meissen porcelain ewer, representative of 'water', was created as part of a series of four ewers, each symbolising a different element.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After the model by J.J. Kaendler, with a relief naval scene, flanked by figures of Neptune, a mermaid and galloping horses, the circular flaring base with spouting dolphins among bulrushes, the underside with under glaze blue crossed swords mark above one cancellation line, incised model number 320 and impressed numerals.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pair ormolu mounted</title>
		<link>/product/pair-of-ormolu-mounted-rare-lithyalin-glass-antique-vases/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 08:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo9.cmsmart.net/antique_3/?post_type=product&#038;p=53</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[These splendid antique vases are a rare example of fine Lithyalin glass used over a large surface area, making the pair an exclusive collectable.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Attributed to the Saint Louis Glassworks (French, f. 1767)</p>
<p>Of ovoid form, the glasses canted and with flared necks and bases, supported by scrolling ormolu mounts to the sides and bases</p>
<p>Lithyalin glass is an opaque or translucent marbled glass with a surface resembling polished gemstones in a wide range of colours. It was first made by the chemist Friedrich Egermann (Bohemian, 1777-1864) in 1828 in northern Bohemia, and he patented the process in 1829. When this patent expired, similar pieces were made in France, Bohemia, China and Russia.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
